

RUSSELL HARBEN

OBJECTIVE

My goal is to use my knowledge and experience in web development and programming to develop real world software and web applications and contribute to teams and organizations who are developing challenging and innovative software and web applications.

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- JQuery
- Firebase
- SOL Server
- Node.js

Strong interpersonal skills and enthusiasm and experience working in a fast-paced, team environments.

EXPERIENCE

DATA ANALYST & FRONTEND DEVELOPER • PLATINUM CIRCLE TECHNOLOGIES • JUNE 2016 - PRESENT

- Design and develop custom GL coding logic using SQL Server 2016
- Design and develop frontend of custom small parcel audit portal used by customers ranging from small to Fortune 500 companies including GPC, Target, Hunter Douglas, McKesson, and more using Visual Studio 2017 and ASP.net
- Account management for GPC's fuel program ranging from customer support to distribution and management of monthly 3PL reconciliation and detail reports as well as monthly and quarterly invoicing

OUTSIDE SALES • SUNSHINE GOLF CAR • JUNE 2014 - FEBRUARY 2016

- The single outside salesperson for a company that generated approximately 6.5 million in yearly revenue
- Sales and customer relationship management for EZ-GO utility vehicles to commercial organizations including schools, professional baseball organizations, farms, municipalities, etc.

ASSISTANT MANAGER • SUNSHINE GOLF CAR • JUNE 2013 - JUNE 2015

- Scheduled and assisted in management of the service department, the company's primary source of revenue
- Assisted in supervision and oversight of daily tasks of 4 shop mechanics, 2 road mechanics, and 1 driver

EDUCATION

BACHELORS IN COMMUNICATIONS • DECEMBER 2010 • UNIVERSITY OF SOUTH ALABAMA
Dean's List Honors and member of University of South Alabama's Division I NCAA Baseball
Team

2005 • MILTON HIGH SCHOOL

Varsity Baseball - 4 year letter recipient Varsity Football - 2 year letter recipient

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE OR LEADERSHIP

2004 - Captain, varsity football team







